{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416507804","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416507804"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 694816f2-2ec6-4702-a92e-1f5570a87695"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kusoma kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416508767","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416508767"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 694816f2-2ec6-4702-a92e-1f5570a87695"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kusoma kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416511703","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416511703"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 694816f2-2ec6-4702-a92e-1f5570a87695"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNATAKA"," userResponse":" KUNATAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416512246","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416512246"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 694816f2-2ec6-4702-a92e-1f5570a87695"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" MACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416512904","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416512904"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 694816f2-2ec6-4702-a92e-1f5570a87695"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAONE"," userResponse":" YAONE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416517095","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416517095"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 694816f2-2ec6-4702-a92e-1f5570a87695"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Masikio yasikie"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASIKIO"," userResponse":" MASIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416518018","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416518017"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 694816f2-2ec6-4702-a92e-1f5570a87695"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Masikio yasikie"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YASIKIE"," userResponse":" YASIKIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416521701","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416521701"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 694816f2-2ec6-4702-a92e-1f5570a87695"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416522483","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416522483"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 694816f2-2ec6-4702-a92e-1f5570a87695"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOMO"," userResponse":" MDOMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416523457","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416523457"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 694816f2-2ec6-4702-a92e-1f5570a87695"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USEME"," userResponse":" USEME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416527356","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416527355"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 694816f2-2ec6-4702-a92e-1f5570a87695"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kusoma kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416528320","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416528320"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 694816f2-2ec6-4702-a92e-1f5570a87695"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kusoma kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416531203","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416531202"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 694816f2-2ec6-4702-a92e-1f5570a87695"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNATAKA"," userResponse":" KUNATAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416531735","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416531735"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 694816f2-2ec6-4702-a92e-1f5570a87695"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" MACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416532378","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416532378"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 694816f2-2ec6-4702-a92e-1f5570a87695"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAONE"," userResponse":" YAONE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416536468","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416536468"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 694816f2-2ec6-4702-a92e-1f5570a87695"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Masikio yasikie"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASIKIO"," userResponse":" MASIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416537402","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416537402"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 694816f2-2ec6-4702-a92e-1f5570a87695"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Masikio yasikie"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YASIKIE"," userResponse":" YASIKIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416541118","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416541117"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 694816f2-2ec6-4702-a92e-1f5570a87695"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416541915","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416541915"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 694816f2-2ec6-4702-a92e-1f5570a87695"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOMO"," userResponse":" MDOMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416542901","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416542900"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 694816f2-2ec6-4702-a92e-1f5570a87695"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USEME"," userResponse":" USEME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416546233","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416546232"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 694816f2-2ec6-4702-a92e-1f5570a87695"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416546329","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416546329"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 694816f2-2ec6-4702-a92e-1f5570a87695"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USEME"," userResponse":" USEME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416569221","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416569221"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" b50568ed-a6d8-479f-ab5d-3d9f0fc21f22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kusoma kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416570199","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416570198"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" b50568ed-a6d8-479f-ab5d-3d9f0fc21f22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kusoma kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416573127","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416573127"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" b50568ed-a6d8-479f-ab5d-3d9f0fc21f22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNATAKA"," userResponse":" KUNATAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416573670","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416573669"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" b50568ed-a6d8-479f-ab5d-3d9f0fc21f22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" MACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416574325","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416574324"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" b50568ed-a6d8-479f-ab5d-3d9f0fc21f22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAONE"," userResponse":" YAONE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416578452","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416578452"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" b50568ed-a6d8-479f-ab5d-3d9f0fc21f22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Masikio yasikie"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASIKIO"," userResponse":" MASIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416579385","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416579384"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" b50568ed-a6d8-479f-ab5d-3d9f0fc21f22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Masikio yasikie"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YASIKIE"," userResponse":" YASIKIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416583041","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416583041"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" b50568ed-a6d8-479f-ab5d-3d9f0fc21f22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416583825","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416583824"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" b50568ed-a6d8-479f-ab5d-3d9f0fc21f22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOMO"," userResponse":" MDOMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416584798","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416584798"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" b50568ed-a6d8-479f-ab5d-3d9f0fc21f22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USEME"," userResponse":" USEME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416588773","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416588772"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" b50568ed-a6d8-479f-ab5d-3d9f0fc21f22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kusoma kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416589747","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416589746"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" b50568ed-a6d8-479f-ab5d-3d9f0fc21f22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kusoma kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416592711","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416592711"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" b50568ed-a6d8-479f-ab5d-3d9f0fc21f22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNATAKA"," userResponse":" KUNATAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416593245","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416593245"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" b50568ed-a6d8-479f-ab5d-3d9f0fc21f22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" MACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416593899","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416593898"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" b50568ed-a6d8-479f-ab5d-3d9f0fc21f22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAONE"," userResponse":" YAONE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416598068","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416598068"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" b50568ed-a6d8-479f-ab5d-3d9f0fc21f22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Masikio yasikie"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASIKIO"," userResponse":" MASIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416599003","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416599002"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" b50568ed-a6d8-479f-ab5d-3d9f0fc21f22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Masikio yasikie"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YASIKIE"," userResponse":" YASIKIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416602668","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416602668"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" b50568ed-a6d8-479f-ab5d-3d9f0fc21f22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416603463","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416603463"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" b50568ed-a6d8-479f-ab5d-3d9f0fc21f22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOMO"," userResponse":" MDOMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416604451","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416604450"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" b50568ed-a6d8-479f-ab5d-3d9f0fc21f22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USEME"," userResponse":" USEME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416607757","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416607754"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" b50568ed-a6d8-479f-ab5d-3d9f0fc21f22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416607856","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416607856"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" b50568ed-a6d8-479f-ab5d-3d9f0fc21f22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USEME"," userResponse":" USEME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416623798","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416623798"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" e1bed379-74e1-4c3e-ad86-c92e2d0e7f3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-9-3"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416635461","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416635461"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" e1bed379-74e1-4c3e-ad86-c92e2d0e7f3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-9-3"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416643272","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416643272"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" e1bed379-74e1-4c3e-ad86-c92e2d0e7f3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-9-3"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416650726","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416650726"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" e1bed379-74e1-4c3e-ad86-c92e2d0e7f3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_9-1-7"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416657593","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416657593"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" e1bed379-74e1-4c3e-ad86-c92e2d0e7f3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_5-1-2"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416662602","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416662602"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" e1bed379-74e1-4c3e-ad86-c92e2d0e7f3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_5-1-2"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416667150","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416667150"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" e1bed379-74e1-4c3e-ad86-c92e2d0e7f3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_5-1-2"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416672739","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416672739"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" e1bed379-74e1-4c3e-ad86-c92e2d0e7f3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_8-3-2"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416681235","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416681235"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" e1bed379-74e1-4c3e-ad86-c92e2d0e7f3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_3-9-4"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416685819","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416685818"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" e1bed379-74e1-4c3e-ad86-c92e2d0e7f3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_3-9-4"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416691186","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416691186"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" e1bed379-74e1-4c3e-ad86-c92e2d0e7f3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_5-0-1"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416697950","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416697949"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" e1bed379-74e1-4c3e-ad86-c92e2d0e7f3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_5-0-1"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416703019","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416703018"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" e1bed379-74e1-4c3e-ad86-c92e2d0e7f3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_5-0-1"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416708941","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416708941"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" e1bed379-74e1-4c3e-ad86-c92e2d0e7f3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_0-6-2"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416723272","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416723272"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" e1bed379-74e1-4c3e-ad86-c92e2d0e7f3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_0-6-2"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416729401","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416729401"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" e1bed379-74e1-4c3e-ad86-c92e2d0e7f3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_0-6-2"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416736707","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416736707"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" e1bed379-74e1-4c3e-ad86-c92e2d0e7f3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_9-4-7"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416742348","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416742348"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" e1bed379-74e1-4c3e-ad86-c92e2d0e7f3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-5-4"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416750569","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416750569"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" e1bed379-74e1-4c3e-ad86-c92e2d0e7f3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-5-4"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416778461","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416778460"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" e1bed379-74e1-4c3e-ad86-c92e2d0e7f3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-5-4"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416787808","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416787808"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 84e0b69f-d039-44f3-be79-d8804496fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninampenda mwalimu wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAMPENDA"," userResponse":" NINAMPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416788552","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416788552"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 84e0b69f-d039-44f3-be79-d8804496fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninampenda mwalimu wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWALIMU"," userResponse":" MWALIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416788998","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416788997"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 84e0b69f-d039-44f3-be79-d8804496fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninampenda mwalimu wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416791859","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416791858"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 84e0b69f-d039-44f3-be79-d8804496fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YEYE"," userResponse":" YEYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416792061","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416792061"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 84e0b69f-d039-44f3-be79-d8804496fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416793059","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416793059"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 84e0b69f-d039-44f3-be79-d8804496fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREMBO"," userResponse":" MREMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416793387","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416793387"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 84e0b69f-d039-44f3-be79-d8804496fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNO"," userResponse":" MNO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416796471","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416796470"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 84e0b69f-d039-44f3-be79-d8804496fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YEYE"," userResponse":" YEYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416796702","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416796702"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 84e0b69f-d039-44f3-be79-d8804496fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416797415","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416797415"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 84e0b69f-d039-44f3-be79-d8804496fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWALIMU"," userResponse":" MWALIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416798328","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416798328"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 84e0b69f-d039-44f3-be79-d8804496fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZURI"," userResponse":" MZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416800350","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416800350"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 84e0b69f-d039-44f3-be79-d8804496fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416800833","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416800833"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 84e0b69f-d039-44f3-be79-d8804496fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416801547","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416801547"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 84e0b69f-d039-44f3-be79-d8804496fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEMA"," userResponse":" MWEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416802151","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416802151"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 84e0b69f-d039-44f3-be79-d8804496fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416802654","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416802654"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 84e0b69f-d039-44f3-be79-d8804496fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" MWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416803607","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416803607"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 84e0b69f-d039-44f3-be79-d8804496fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUBIRA"," userResponse":" SUBIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416807217","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416807217"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 84e0b69f-d039-44f3-be79-d8804496fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivyosuka nywele zake zinapendeza sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIVYOSUKA"," userResponse":" ALIVYOSUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416807679","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416807679"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 84e0b69f-d039-44f3-be79-d8804496fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivyosuka nywele zake zinapendeza sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYWELE"," userResponse":" NYWELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416808392","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416808392"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 84e0b69f-d039-44f3-be79-d8804496fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivyosuka nywele zake zinapendeza sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416809956","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416809956"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 84e0b69f-d039-44f3-be79-d8804496fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivyosuka nywele zake zinapendeza sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZINAPENDEZA"," userResponse":" ZINAPENDEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416810498","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416810498"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 84e0b69f-d039-44f3-be79-d8804496fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivyosuka nywele zake zinapendeza sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416814462","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416814462"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 84e0b69f-d039-44f3-be79-d8804496fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Amezipamba na shanga za rangirangi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEZIPAMBA"," userResponse":" AMEZIPAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416814765","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416814765"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 84e0b69f-d039-44f3-be79-d8804496fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Amezipamba na shanga za rangirangi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416815488","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416815488"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 84e0b69f-d039-44f3-be79-d8804496fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Amezipamba na shanga za rangirangi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHANGA"," userResponse":" SHANGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416815770","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416815770"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 84e0b69f-d039-44f3-be79-d8804496fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Amezipamba na shanga za rangirangi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416816843","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416816843"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 84e0b69f-d039-44f3-be79-d8804496fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Amezipamba na shanga za rangirangi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGIRANGI"," userResponse":" RANGIRANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416819779","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416819778"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 84e0b69f-d039-44f3-be79-d8804496fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHANGA"," userResponse":" SHANGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416820542","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416820542"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 84e0b69f-d039-44f3-be79-d8804496fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416820834","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416820834"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 84e0b69f-d039-44f3-be79-d8804496fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416821038","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416821038"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 84e0b69f-d039-44f3-be79-d8804496fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416821611","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416821610"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 84e0b69f-d039-44f3-be79-d8804496fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416821854","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416821854"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 84e0b69f-d039-44f3-be79-d8804496fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416822798","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416822798"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 84e0b69f-d039-44f3-be79-d8804496fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANI"," userResponse":" KIJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416824221","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416824221"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 84e0b69f-d039-44f3-be79-d8804496fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEUPE"," userResponse":" NYEUPE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416825579","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416825578"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 84e0b69f-d039-44f3-be79-d8804496fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEKUNDU"," userResponse":" NYEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416826245","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416826245"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 84e0b69f-d039-44f3-be79-d8804496fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416827120","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416827119"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 84e0b69f-d039-44f3-be79-d8804496fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANJANO"," userResponse":" MANJANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416830169","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416830168"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 84e0b69f-d039-44f3-be79-d8804496fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama tafadhali nisukie nywele zangu ziwe kama za mwalimu wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416831613","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416831612"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 84e0b69f-d039-44f3-be79-d8804496fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama tafadhali nisukie nywele zangu ziwe kama za mwalimu wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" TAFADHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416832545","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416832545"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 84e0b69f-d039-44f3-be79-d8804496fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama tafadhali nisukie nywele zangu ziwe kama za mwalimu wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NISUKIE"," userResponse":" NISUKIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416832929","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416832928"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 84e0b69f-d039-44f3-be79-d8804496fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama tafadhali nisukie nywele zangu ziwe kama za mwalimu wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYWELE"," userResponse":" NYWELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416833589","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416833588"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 84e0b69f-d039-44f3-be79-d8804496fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama tafadhali nisukie nywele zangu ziwe kama za mwalimu wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZANGU"," userResponse":" ZANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416834099","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416834099"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 84e0b69f-d039-44f3-be79-d8804496fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama tafadhali nisukie nywele zangu ziwe kama za mwalimu wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIWE"," userResponse":" ZIWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416834635","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416834634"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 84e0b69f-d039-44f3-be79-d8804496fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama tafadhali nisukie nywele zangu ziwe kama za mwalimu wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416834861","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416834860"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 84e0b69f-d039-44f3-be79-d8804496fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama tafadhali nisukie nywele zangu ziwe kama za mwalimu wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416835627","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416835627"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 84e0b69f-d039-44f3-be79-d8804496fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama tafadhali nisukie nywele zangu ziwe kama za mwalimu wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWALIMU"," userResponse":" MWALIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416836060","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416836060"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 84e0b69f-d039-44f3-be79-d8804496fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama tafadhali nisukie nywele zangu ziwe kama za mwalimu wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416839611","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416839611"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 84e0b69f-d039-44f3-be79-d8804496fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningekuwa na umri zaidi ningezipamba nywele zangu kwa shanga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINGEKUWA"," userResponse":" NINGEKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416839922","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416839922"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 84e0b69f-d039-44f3-be79-d8804496fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningekuwa na umri zaidi ningezipamba nywele zangu kwa shanga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416840578","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416840577"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 84e0b69f-d039-44f3-be79-d8804496fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningekuwa na umri zaidi ningezipamba nywele zangu kwa shanga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMRI"," userResponse":" UMRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416841536","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416841535"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 84e0b69f-d039-44f3-be79-d8804496fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningekuwa na umri zaidi ningezipamba nywele zangu kwa shanga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416843301","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416843301"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 84e0b69f-d039-44f3-be79-d8804496fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningekuwa na umri zaidi ningezipamba nywele zangu kwa shanga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINGEZIPAMBA"," userResponse":" NINGEZIPAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416843881","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416843880"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 84e0b69f-d039-44f3-be79-d8804496fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningekuwa na umri zaidi ningezipamba nywele zangu kwa shanga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYWELE"," userResponse":" NYWELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416844516","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416844516"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 84e0b69f-d039-44f3-be79-d8804496fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningekuwa na umri zaidi ningezipamba nywele zangu kwa shanga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZANGU"," userResponse":" ZANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416844729","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416844729"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 84e0b69f-d039-44f3-be79-d8804496fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningekuwa na umri zaidi ningezipamba nywele zangu kwa shanga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416845373","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416845373"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 84e0b69f-d039-44f3-be79-d8804496fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningekuwa na umri zaidi ningezipamba nywele zangu kwa shanga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHANGA"," userResponse":" SHANGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416849001","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416849001"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 84e0b69f-d039-44f3-be79-d8804496fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakua sawa kabisa na mwalimu wangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAKUA"," userResponse":" NITAKUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416849564","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416849564"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 84e0b69f-d039-44f3-be79-d8804496fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakua sawa kabisa na mwalimu wangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAWA"," userResponse":" SAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416850678","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416850678"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 84e0b69f-d039-44f3-be79-d8804496fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakua sawa kabisa na mwalimu wangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KABISA"," userResponse":" KABISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416851270","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416851270"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 84e0b69f-d039-44f3-be79-d8804496fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakua sawa kabisa na mwalimu wangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416852015","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416852015"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 84e0b69f-d039-44f3-be79-d8804496fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakua sawa kabisa na mwalimu wangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWALIMU"," userResponse":" MWALIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416852458","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416852457"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 84e0b69f-d039-44f3-be79-d8804496fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakua sawa kabisa na mwalimu wangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416855212","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416855210"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 84e0b69f-d039-44f3-be79-d8804496fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Nitakua sawa kabisa na mwalimu wangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416855298","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416855298"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 84e0b69f-d039-44f3-be79-d8804496fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakua sawa kabisa na mwalimu wangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.show.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416860037","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416860037"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 84e0b69f-d039-44f3-be79-d8804496fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Nitakua sawa kabisa na mwalimu wangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Counting_Fingers_Toes__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416864519","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416864519"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 84e0b69f-d039-44f3-be79-d8804496fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Nitakua sawa kabisa na mwalimu wangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Counting_Fingers_Toes__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416875678","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416875677"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 8bc1d4e0-c0aa-437e-853b-8e22255791c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Counting_Fingers_Toes__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vidole vya mikono yangu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIDOLE"," userResponse":" VIDOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Counting_Fingers_Toes__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416875882","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416875882"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 8bc1d4e0-c0aa-437e-853b-8e22255791c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Counting_Fingers_Toes__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vidole vya mikono yangu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYA"," userResponse":" VYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Counting_Fingers_Toes__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416876702","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416876702"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 8bc1d4e0-c0aa-437e-853b-8e22255791c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Counting_Fingers_Toes__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vidole vya mikono yangu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKONO"," userResponse":" MIKONO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Counting_Fingers_Toes__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416877356","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416877355"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 8bc1d4e0-c0aa-437e-853b-8e22255791c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Counting_Fingers_Toes__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vidole vya mikono yangu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Counting_Fingers_Toes__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416880703","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416880703"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 8bc1d4e0-c0aa-437e-853b-8e22255791c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Counting_Fingers_Toes__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jumla yake kumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUMLA"," userResponse":" JUMLA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Counting_Fingers_Toes__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416881196","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416881196"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 8bc1d4e0-c0aa-437e-853b-8e22255791c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Counting_Fingers_Toes__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jumla yake kumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Counting_Fingers_Toes__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416881648","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416881647"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 8bc1d4e0-c0aa-437e-853b-8e22255791c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Counting_Fingers_Toes__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jumla yake kumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMI"," userResponse":" KUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Counting_Fingers_Toes__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416884732","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416884730"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 8bc1d4e0-c0aa-437e-853b-8e22255791c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Counting_Fingers_Toes__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huku tano na huku tano"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Counting_Fingers_Toes__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416885408","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416885407"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 8bc1d4e0-c0aa-437e-853b-8e22255791c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Counting_Fingers_Toes__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huku tano na huku tano"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Counting_Fingers_Toes__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416885689","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416885688"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 8bc1d4e0-c0aa-437e-853b-8e22255791c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Counting_Fingers_Toes__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huku tano na huku tano"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Counting_Fingers_Toes__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416885936","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416885936"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 8bc1d4e0-c0aa-437e-853b-8e22255791c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Counting_Fingers_Toes__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huku tano na huku tano"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Counting_Fingers_Toes__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416886581","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416886581"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 8bc1d4e0-c0aa-437e-853b-8e22255791c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Counting_Fingers_Toes__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huku tano na huku tano"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Counting_Fingers_Toes__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416889555","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416889555"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 8bc1d4e0-c0aa-437e-853b-8e22255791c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Counting_Fingers_Toes__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jumla yake kumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUMLA"," userResponse":" JUMLA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Counting_Fingers_Toes__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416890047","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416890046"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 8bc1d4e0-c0aa-437e-853b-8e22255791c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Counting_Fingers_Toes__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jumla yake kumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Counting_Fingers_Toes__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416890500","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416890499"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 8bc1d4e0-c0aa-437e-853b-8e22255791c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Counting_Fingers_Toes__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jumla yake kumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMI"," userResponse":" KUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Counting_Fingers_Toes__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416894321","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416894320"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 8bc1d4e0-c0aa-437e-853b-8e22255791c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Counting_Fingers_Toes__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jumla yake kumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIDOLE"," userResponse":" VIDOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Counting_Fingers_Toes__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416894494","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416894493"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 8bc1d4e0-c0aa-437e-853b-8e22255791c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Counting_Fingers_Toes__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jumla yake kumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYA"," userResponse":" VYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Counting_Fingers_Toes__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416895299","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416895299"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 8bc1d4e0-c0aa-437e-853b-8e22255791c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Counting_Fingers_Toes__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jumla yake kumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIGUU"," userResponse":" MIGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Counting_Fingers_Toes__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416896029","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416896029"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 8bc1d4e0-c0aa-437e-853b-8e22255791c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Counting_Fingers_Toes__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jumla yake kumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Counting_Fingers_Toes__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416898597","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416898596"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 8bc1d4e0-c0aa-437e-853b-8e22255791c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Counting_Fingers_Toes__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jumla yake kumi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUMLA"," userResponse":" JUMLA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Counting_Fingers_Toes__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416899088","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416899088"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 8bc1d4e0-c0aa-437e-853b-8e22255791c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Counting_Fingers_Toes__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jumla yake kumi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Counting_Fingers_Toes__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416899543","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416899542"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 8bc1d4e0-c0aa-437e-853b-8e22255791c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Counting_Fingers_Toes__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jumla yake kumi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMI"," userResponse":" KUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Counting_Fingers_Toes__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416902639","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416902638"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 8bc1d4e0-c0aa-437e-853b-8e22255791c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Counting_Fingers_Toes__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huku tano na huku tano"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Counting_Fingers_Toes__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416903322","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416903322"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 8bc1d4e0-c0aa-437e-853b-8e22255791c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Counting_Fingers_Toes__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huku tano na huku tano"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Counting_Fingers_Toes__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416903598","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416903598"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 8bc1d4e0-c0aa-437e-853b-8e22255791c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Counting_Fingers_Toes__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huku tano na huku tano"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Counting_Fingers_Toes__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416903844","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416903842"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 8bc1d4e0-c0aa-437e-853b-8e22255791c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Counting_Fingers_Toes__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huku tano na huku tano"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Counting_Fingers_Toes__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416904489","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416904488"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 8bc1d4e0-c0aa-437e-853b-8e22255791c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Counting_Fingers_Toes__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huku tano na huku tano"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Counting_Fingers_Toes__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416907502","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416907502"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 8bc1d4e0-c0aa-437e-853b-8e22255791c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Counting_Fingers_Toes__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jumla yake kumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUMLA"," userResponse":" JUMLA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Counting_Fingers_Toes__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416907994","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416907993"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 8bc1d4e0-c0aa-437e-853b-8e22255791c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Counting_Fingers_Toes__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jumla yake kumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Counting_Fingers_Toes__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416908445","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416908444"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 8bc1d4e0-c0aa-437e-853b-8e22255791c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Counting_Fingers_Toes__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jumla yake kumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMI"," userResponse":" KUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Counting_Fingers_Toes__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416911406","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416911405"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 8bc1d4e0-c0aa-437e-853b-8e22255791c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Counting_Fingers_Toes__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Jumla yake kumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416911504","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416911504"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 8bc1d4e0-c0aa-437e-853b-8e22255791c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Counting_Fingers_Toes__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jumla yake kumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMI"," userResponse":" KUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416918328","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416918328"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 8bc1d4e0-c0aa-437e-853b-8e22255791c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Counting_Fingers_Toes__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Jumla yake kumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416929270","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416929269"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 9a4314fa-92bd-4b98-8099-f8fa0759b0c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mtoto analia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416929781","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416929780"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 9a4314fa-92bd-4b98-8099-f8fa0759b0c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mtoto analia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416930486","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416930485"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 9a4314fa-92bd-4b98-8099-f8fa0759b0c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mtoto analia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416931536","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416931535"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 9a4314fa-92bd-4b98-8099-f8fa0759b0c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kwa nini mtoto analia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416931616","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416931615"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 9a4314fa-92bd-4b98-8099-f8fa0759b0c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mtoto analia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416937243","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416937243"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 9a4314fa-92bd-4b98-8099-f8fa0759b0c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kwa nini mtoto analia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416946767","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416946767"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 79672f8d-695c-43a3-a5e3-fe9c24330fbc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416949255","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416949255"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 79672f8d-695c-43a3-a5e3-fe9c24330fbc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416949325","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416949325"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 79672f8d-695c-43a3-a5e3-fe9c24330fbc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416955641","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416955641"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 0d9c8a4a-1eab-4f4a-b5ae-9754d12b342d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416963025","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416963025"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 0d9c8a4a-1eab-4f4a-b5ae-9754d12b342d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416963094","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416963094"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 0d9c8a4a-1eab-4f4a-b5ae-9754d12b342d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416969064","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416969064"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 0d9c8a4a-1eab-4f4a-b5ae-9754d12b342d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416979031","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416979031"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" ad4b109b-335b-4b81-b95b-c52a1402b5cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416979623","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416979623"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" ad4b109b-335b-4b81-b95b-c52a1402b5cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416980545","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416980545"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" ad4b109b-335b-4b81-b95b-c52a1402b5cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMISI"," userResponse":" HAMISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416980698","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416980698"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" ad4b109b-335b-4b81-b95b-c52a1402b5cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416981412","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416981411"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" ad4b109b-335b-4b81-b95b-c52a1402b5cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABAKE"," userResponse":" BABAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416982106","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416982105"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" ad4b109b-335b-4b81-b95b-c52a1402b5cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIENDA"," userResponse":" WALIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416982823","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416982822"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" ad4b109b-335b-4b81-b95b-c52a1402b5cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNUNUA"," userResponse":" KUNUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416983407","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416983406"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" ad4b109b-335b-4b81-b95b-c52a1402b5cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SARE"," userResponse":" SARE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416983637","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416983637"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" ad4b109b-335b-4b81-b95b-c52a1402b5cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416984139","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416984139"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" ad4b109b-335b-4b81-b95b-c52a1402b5cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416987576","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416987575"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" ad4b109b-335b-4b81-b95b-c52a1402b5cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAONEKANA"," userResponse":" ANAONEKANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416988089","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416988089"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" ad4b109b-335b-4b81-b95b-c52a1402b5cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZURI"," userResponse":" MZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416988693","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416988693"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" ad4b109b-335b-4b81-b95b-c52a1402b5cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416989510","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416989509"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" ad4b109b-335b-4b81-b95b-c52a1402b5cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMISI"," userResponse":" HAMISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416990410","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416990409"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" ad4b109b-335b-4b81-b95b-c52a1402b5cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFIKIRIA"," userResponse":" ALIFIKIRIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416993418","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416993418"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" ad4b109b-335b-4b81-b95b-c52a1402b5cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHATI"," userResponse":" SHATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416993840","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416993840"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" ad4b109b-335b-4b81-b95b-c52a1402b5cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILI"," userResponse":" HILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416993953","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416993953"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" ad4b109b-335b-4b81-b95b-c52a1402b5cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416994388","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416994388"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" ad4b109b-335b-4b81-b95b-c52a1402b5cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFI"," userResponse":" SAFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416994892","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416994892"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" ad4b109b-335b-4b81-b95b-c52a1402b5cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416995677","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416995676"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" ad4b109b-335b-4b81-b95b-c52a1402b5cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMISI"," userResponse":" HAMISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416996350","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416996350"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" ad4b109b-335b-4b81-b95b-c52a1402b5cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416999563","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416999562"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" ad4b109b-335b-4b81-b95b-c52a1402b5cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" TAFADHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417000242","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417000241"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" ad4b109b-335b-4b81-b95b-c52a1402b5cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417001375","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417001374"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" ad4b109b-335b-4b81-b95b-c52a1402b5cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINUNULIE"," userResponse":" NINUNULIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417001920","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417001920"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" ad4b109b-335b-4b81-b95b-c52a1402b5cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHATI"," userResponse":" SHATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417002115","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417002114"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" ad4b109b-335b-4b81-b95b-c52a1402b5cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417002747","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417002747"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" ad4b109b-335b-4b81-b95b-c52a1402b5cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANI"," userResponse":" KIJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417003675","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417003675"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" ad4b109b-335b-4b81-b95b-c52a1402b5cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBICHI"," userResponse":" KIBICHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417004462","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417004461"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" ad4b109b-335b-4b81-b95b-c52a1402b5cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMISI"," userResponse":" HAMISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417005154","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417005154"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" ad4b109b-335b-4b81-b95b-c52a1402b5cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALILIA"," userResponse":" ALILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417008096","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417008095"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" ad4b109b-335b-4b81-b95b-c52a1402b5cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ninanunua sare ya shule pekee baba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LEO"," userResponse":" LEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417009159","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417009159"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" ad4b109b-335b-4b81-b95b-c52a1402b5cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ninanunua sare ya shule pekee baba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINANUNUA"," userResponse":" NINANUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417009941","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417009941"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" ad4b109b-335b-4b81-b95b-c52a1402b5cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ninanunua sare ya shule pekee baba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SARE"," userResponse":" SARE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417010113","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417010112"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" ad4b109b-335b-4b81-b95b-c52a1402b5cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ninanunua sare ya shule pekee baba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417010543","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417010543"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" ad4b109b-335b-4b81-b95b-c52a1402b5cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ninanunua sare ya shule pekee baba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417011616","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417011616"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" ad4b109b-335b-4b81-b95b-c52a1402b5cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ninanunua sare ya shule pekee baba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEKEE"," userResponse":" PEKEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417012824","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417012824"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" ad4b109b-335b-4b81-b95b-c52a1402b5cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ninanunua sare ya shule pekee baba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417013568","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417013568"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" ad4b109b-335b-4b81-b95b-c52a1402b5cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ninanunua sare ya shule pekee baba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417016490","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417016487"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" ad4b109b-335b-4b81-b95b-c52a1402b5cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SINA"," userResponse":" SINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417016850","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417016850"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" ad4b109b-335b-4b81-b95b-c52a1402b5cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PESA"," userResponse":" PESA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417017622","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417017622"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" ad4b109b-335b-4b81-b95b-c52a1402b5cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZINGINE"," userResponse":" ZINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417017987","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417017986"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" ad4b109b-335b-4b81-b95b-c52a1402b5cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417018637","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417018637"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" ad4b109b-335b-4b81-b95b-c52a1402b5cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNUNUA"," userResponse":" KUNUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417019172","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417019171"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" ad4b109b-335b-4b81-b95b-c52a1402b5cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHATI"," userResponse":" SHATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417019530","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417019529"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" ad4b109b-335b-4b81-b95b-c52a1402b5cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417020038","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417020037"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" ad4b109b-335b-4b81-b95b-c52a1402b5cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" HILO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417020881","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417020881"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" ad4b109b-335b-4b81-b95b-c52a1402b5cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417021595","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417021595"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" ad4b109b-335b-4b81-b95b-c52a1402b5cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417022109","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417022109"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" ad4b109b-335b-4b81-b95b-c52a1402b5cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417025407","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417025407"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" ad4b109b-335b-4b81-b95b-c52a1402b5cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417026423","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417026422"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" ad4b109b-335b-4b81-b95b-c52a1402b5cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" KULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417026652","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417026650"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" ad4b109b-335b-4b81-b95b-c52a1402b5cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417027211","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417027210"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" ad4b109b-335b-4b81-b95b-c52a1402b5cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PESA"," userResponse":" PESA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417028504","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417028503"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" ad4b109b-335b-4b81-b95b-c52a1402b5cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIZOBAKI"," userResponse":" ZILIZOBAKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417028954","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417028954"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" ad4b109b-335b-4b81-b95b-c52a1402b5cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417029708","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417029707"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" ad4b109b-335b-4b81-b95b-c52a1402b5cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNUNUA"," userResponse":" KUNUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417030239","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417030238"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" ad4b109b-335b-4b81-b95b-c52a1402b5cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHATI"," userResponse":" SHATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417030405","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417030405"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" ad4b109b-335b-4b81-b95b-c52a1402b5cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417031008","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417031008"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" ad4b109b-335b-4b81-b95b-c52a1402b5cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANI"," userResponse":" KIJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417031884","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417031883"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" ad4b109b-335b-4b81-b95b-c52a1402b5cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBICHI"," userResponse":" KIBICHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417035246","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417035246"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" ad4b109b-335b-4b81-b95b-c52a1402b5cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hamisi alifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMISI"," userResponse":" HAMISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417036640","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417036639"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" ad4b109b-335b-4b81-b95b-c52a1402b5cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hamisi alifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFURAHI"," userResponse":" ALIFURAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417037606","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417037606"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" ad4b109b-335b-4b81-b95b-c52a1402b5cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hamisi alifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417040456","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417040454"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" ad4b109b-335b-4b81-b95b-c52a1402b5cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Hamisi alifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417040537","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417040536"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" ad4b109b-335b-4b81-b95b-c52a1402b5cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hamisi alifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417049793","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417049793"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" ad4b109b-335b-4b81-b95b-c52a1402b5cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hamisi alifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417064935","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417064934"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 525d6235-91fd-4461-910d-d927c73c2e75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417065526","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417065525"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 525d6235-91fd-4461-910d-d927c73c2e75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417066447","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417066447"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 525d6235-91fd-4461-910d-d927c73c2e75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMISI"," userResponse":" HAMISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417066591","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417066591"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 525d6235-91fd-4461-910d-d927c73c2e75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417067310","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417067310"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 525d6235-91fd-4461-910d-d927c73c2e75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABAKE"," userResponse":" BABAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417068007","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417068007"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 525d6235-91fd-4461-910d-d927c73c2e75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIENDA"," userResponse":" WALIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417068730","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417068730"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 525d6235-91fd-4461-910d-d927c73c2e75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNUNUA"," userResponse":" KUNUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417069309","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417069309"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 525d6235-91fd-4461-910d-d927c73c2e75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SARE"," userResponse":" SARE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417069546","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417069546"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 525d6235-91fd-4461-910d-d927c73c2e75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417070048","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417070048"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 525d6235-91fd-4461-910d-d927c73c2e75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417073504","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417073504"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 525d6235-91fd-4461-910d-d927c73c2e75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAONEKANA"," userResponse":" ANAONEKANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417074029","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417074028"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 525d6235-91fd-4461-910d-d927c73c2e75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZURI"," userResponse":" MZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417074643","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417074642"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 525d6235-91fd-4461-910d-d927c73c2e75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417075455","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417075454"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 525d6235-91fd-4461-910d-d927c73c2e75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMISI"," userResponse":" HAMISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417075933","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417075933"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 525d6235-91fd-4461-910d-d927c73c2e75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417076005","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417076004"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 525d6235-91fd-4461-910d-d927c73c2e75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMISI"," userResponse":" HAMISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417080722","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417080722"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 525d6235-91fd-4461-910d-d927c73c2e75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417086430","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417086430"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 525d6235-91fd-4461-910d-d927c73c2e75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417093371","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417093371"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 525d6235-91fd-4461-910d-d927c73c2e75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417102491","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417102490"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 525d6235-91fd-4461-910d-d927c73c2e75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417113880","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417113880"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 04677c4e-45f7-41df-ad8d-f3d5ac4c4a60"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CHUI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUI"," userResponse":" CHUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417117972","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417117972"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 04677c4e-45f7-41df-ad8d-f3d5ac4c4a60"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CHUI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417119576","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417119575"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 04677c4e-45f7-41df-ad8d-f3d5ac4c4a60"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CHAKULA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417123536","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417123535"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 04677c4e-45f7-41df-ad8d-f3d5ac4c4a60"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CHAKULA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417125134","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417125134"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 04677c4e-45f7-41df-ad8d-f3d5ac4c4a60"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CHOMBO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHOMBO"," userResponse":" CHOMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417130199","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417130199"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 04677c4e-45f7-41df-ad8d-f3d5ac4c4a60"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CHOMBO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHOMBO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417131800","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417131800"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 04677c4e-45f7-41df-ad8d-f3d5ac4c4a60"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CHUNGU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" CHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417136417","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417136417"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 04677c4e-45f7-41df-ad8d-f3d5ac4c4a60"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CHUNGU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417138047","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417138047"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 04677c4e-45f7-41df-ad8d-f3d5ac4c4a60"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CHIPSI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHIPSI"," userResponse":" CHIPSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417142285","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417142284"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 04677c4e-45f7-41df-ad8d-f3d5ac4c4a60"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CHIPSI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHIPSI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417143896","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417143895"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 04677c4e-45f7-41df-ad8d-f3d5ac4c4a60"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CHAI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAI"," userResponse":" CHAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417146516","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417146515"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 04677c4e-45f7-41df-ad8d-f3d5ac4c4a60"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CHAI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAI"," userResponse":" CHAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417148103","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417148102"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 04677c4e-45f7-41df-ad8d-f3d5ac4c4a60"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CHUNGWA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGWA"," userResponse":" CHUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417155387","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417155387"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 04677c4e-45f7-41df-ad8d-f3d5ac4c4a60"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CHUNGWA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417156984","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417156983"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 04677c4e-45f7-41df-ad8d-f3d5ac4c4a60"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CHURA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHURA"," userResponse":" CHURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417161992","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417161992"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 04677c4e-45f7-41df-ad8d-f3d5ac4c4a60"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CHURA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHURA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417163574","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417163574"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 04677c4e-45f7-41df-ad8d-f3d5ac4c4a60"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CHOO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHOO"," userResponse":" CHOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417166247","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417166247"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 04677c4e-45f7-41df-ad8d-f3d5ac4c4a60"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CHOO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHOO"," userResponse":" CHOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417167825","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417167825"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 04677c4e-45f7-41df-ad8d-f3d5ac4c4a60"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CHAPATI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAPATI"," userResponse":" CHAPATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417174341","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417174341"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 04677c4e-45f7-41df-ad8d-f3d5ac4c4a60"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CHAPATI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAPATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417176371","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417176371"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 04677c4e-45f7-41df-ad8d-f3d5ac4c4a60"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" CHAPATI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417176521","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417176521"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 04677c4e-45f7-41df-ad8d-f3d5ac4c4a60"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CHAPATI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAPATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417183338","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417183338"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 04677c4e-45f7-41df-ad8d-f3d5ac4c4a60"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" CHAPATI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417188323","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417188323"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 04677c4e-45f7-41df-ad8d-f3d5ac4c4a60"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" CHAPATI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417194788","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417194788"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 04677c4e-45f7-41df-ad8d-f3d5ac4c4a60"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" CHAPATI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417201976","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417201976"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 04677c4e-45f7-41df-ad8d-f3d5ac4c4a60"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" CHAPATI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417211667","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417211667"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" c1e42f91-3bc1-4fa8-aa56-960b60259dc2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_2-1-4"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417216798","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417216798"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" c1e42f91-3bc1-4fa8-aa56-960b60259dc2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_3-1-2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417222424","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417222424"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" c1e42f91-3bc1-4fa8-aa56-960b60259dc2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_3-1-2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417227660","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417227660"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" c1e42f91-3bc1-4fa8-aa56-960b60259dc2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_1-3-4"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417233604","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417233603"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" c1e42f91-3bc1-4fa8-aa56-960b60259dc2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_1-2-4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417238485","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417238485"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" c1e42f91-3bc1-4fa8-aa56-960b60259dc2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_2-1-3"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417245356","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417245356"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" c1e42f91-3bc1-4fa8-aa56-960b60259dc2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_1-4-2"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417259880","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417259880"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" c1e42f91-3bc1-4fa8-aa56-960b60259dc2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-4-1"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417265045","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417265045"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" c1e42f91-3bc1-4fa8-aa56-960b60259dc2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-4-1"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417270791","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417270791"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" c1e42f91-3bc1-4fa8-aa56-960b60259dc2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-4-1"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417276452","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417276452"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" c1e42f91-3bc1-4fa8-aa56-960b60259dc2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_1-4-2"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417281160","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417281160"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" c1e42f91-3bc1-4fa8-aa56-960b60259dc2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_3-4-1"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417285977","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417285977"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" c1e42f91-3bc1-4fa8-aa56-960b60259dc2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_3-4-1"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417291877","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417291877"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" c1e42f91-3bc1-4fa8-aa56-960b60259dc2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_3-4-1"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417298151","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417298151"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" c1e42f91-3bc1-4fa8-aa56-960b60259dc2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_4-2-3"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417303712","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417303712"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" c1e42f91-3bc1-4fa8-aa56-960b60259dc2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_4-2-3"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417308510","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417308510"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" c1e42f91-3bc1-4fa8-aa56-960b60259dc2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_4-2-3"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417315251","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417315250"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" c1e42f91-3bc1-4fa8-aa56-960b60259dc2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_2_4-2-3"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417324387","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417324387"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 2d414497-e4da-416d-9fc1-60d4ea719885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417327034","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417327034"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 2d414497-e4da-416d-9fc1-60d4ea719885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417328602","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417328602"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 2d414497-e4da-416d-9fc1-60d4ea719885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417331601","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417331601"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 2d414497-e4da-416d-9fc1-60d4ea719885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417333166","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417333166"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 2d414497-e4da-416d-9fc1-60d4ea719885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417337679","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417337679"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 2d414497-e4da-416d-9fc1-60d4ea719885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417339256","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417339256"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 2d414497-e4da-416d-9fc1-60d4ea719885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417342111","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417342111"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 2d414497-e4da-416d-9fc1-60d4ea719885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417343660","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417343660"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 2d414497-e4da-416d-9fc1-60d4ea719885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417346574","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417346574"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 2d414497-e4da-416d-9fc1-60d4ea719885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417348159","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417348158"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 2d414497-e4da-416d-9fc1-60d4ea719885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417352080","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417352080"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 2d414497-e4da-416d-9fc1-60d4ea719885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417352851","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417352851"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 2d414497-e4da-416d-9fc1-60d4ea719885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417353647","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417353647"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 2d414497-e4da-416d-9fc1-60d4ea719885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417383064","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417383063"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 2d414497-e4da-416d-9fc1-60d4ea719885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417383212","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417383212"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 2d414497-e4da-416d-9fc1-60d4ea719885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417389818","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417389817"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 2d414497-e4da-416d-9fc1-60d4ea719885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417396290","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417396290"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 2d414497-e4da-416d-9fc1-60d4ea719885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417405698","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417405698"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 48c28194-969a-4cff-8192-79485357bbbc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_3-1-2"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417410978","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417410978"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 48c28194-969a-4cff-8192-79485357bbbc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_3-1-2"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417415989","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417415989"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 48c28194-969a-4cff-8192-79485357bbbc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_1-2-3"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417421169","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417421169"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 48c28194-969a-4cff-8192-79485357bbbc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-4-2"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417426034","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417426034"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 48c28194-969a-4cff-8192-79485357bbbc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-4-2"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417431454","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417431454"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 48c28194-969a-4cff-8192-79485357bbbc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_2-4-3"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417436134","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417436134"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 48c28194-969a-4cff-8192-79485357bbbc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_4-1-3"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417440964","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417440964"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 48c28194-969a-4cff-8192-79485357bbbc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_2-1-4"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417446658","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417446658"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 48c28194-969a-4cff-8192-79485357bbbc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_2-1-3"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417451599","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417451599"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 48c28194-969a-4cff-8192-79485357bbbc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_2-1-3"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417456807","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417456807"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 48c28194-969a-4cff-8192-79485357bbbc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_1-4-3"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417462045","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417462045"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 48c28194-969a-4cff-8192-79485357bbbc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_4_1-4-3"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417467457","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417467457"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 48c28194-969a-4cff-8192-79485357bbbc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_4_1-4-3"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417473057","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417473056"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 48c28194-969a-4cff-8192-79485357bbbc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_4_1-4-3"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417479369","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417479368"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 48c28194-969a-4cff-8192-79485357bbbc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_4_1-4-3"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417487471","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417487471"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 48c28194-969a-4cff-8192-79485357bbbc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_4_1-4-3"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417493995","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417493995"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" 48c28194-969a-4cff-8192-79485357bbbc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_4_1-4-3"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417505749","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417505749"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" c23a3481-40b4-4ecf-868b-1338d11de023"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417507839","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417507839"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" c23a3481-40b4-4ecf-868b-1338d11de023"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417509931","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417509931"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" c23a3481-40b4-4ecf-868b-1338d11de023"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417510064","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417510064"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" c23a3481-40b4-4ecf-868b-1338d11de023"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548417510145","data":{"timestamp":" 1548417510145"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_143800"," gameId":" c23a3481-40b4-4ecf-868b-1338d11de023"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}